const e={sections:[{header:{text:"Choose the right degree of adjectives"},exercises:[{type:"test",question:"Home-made food is ____ than food from a restaurant.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"better",2:"best",3:"more good",4:"gooder"}},{type:"test",question:"Watching a movie is ____ than reading a book.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"more interesting",2:"most interesting",3:"the most interesting",4:"intresting"}},{type:"test",question:"Ann is ____ girl I know.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"the prettiest",2:"the prettyest",3:"prettiest",4:"pretty"}},{type:"test",question:"Jerry is ____ in our family.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"the youngest",2:"young",3:"younger",4:"the younger"}},{type:"test",question:"People in the village are ____ than they are in the city.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Friendlier",2:"the friendliest",3:"friendlier",4:"the most friendliest"}},{type:"test",question:"Larry is five years ____ than Martin.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"older",2:"oldest",3:"more old",4:"less old"}},{type:"test",question:"Learning English is ____ than learning Chinese.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"easier",2:"the easiest",3:"more easier",4:"easy"}},{type:"test",question:"Harry is ____ than Nick.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Taller",2:"more tall",3:"the tallest",4:"tall"}},{type:"test",question:"My mom is ____ mother in the world.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"the best",2:"best",3:"most good",4:"more good"}},{type:"test",question:"Russia is ____ country in the world.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"the biggest",2:"big",3:"biggest",4:"the biggest"}},{type:"test",question:"This bag is ____ than that one?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"more expensive",2:"the most expensive",3:"expensiver",4:"expensive"}},{type:"test",question:"This is the ____ day of my life.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"best",2:"betterest",3:"goddest",4:"better"}},{type:"test",question:"Your English is getting ____",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"better",2:"more good",3:"godder",4:"good"}},{type:"test",question:"Maths is ____ than science.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"easier",2:"more easy",3:"more easier",4:"easy"}},{type:"test",question:"Who is ____ tennis player in this class?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"the best",2:"the better",3:"the good",4:"better than"}}]}]};export{e as default};
